# Sample data
questions_data = [{"question": "Mohamed Salah is a talented player who has achieved marvellous success; he is really a living\u2026\u2026\u2026. .", "choices": ["lie", "legend", "superstition", "fable"], "correct_answer": "legend"}, {"question": "To achieve more success, you will need a lot of perseverance. \"Perseverance\" is the synonym for \".\u2026\u2026\u2026. \".", "choices": ["carelessness", "cleverness", "determination", "deterioration"], "correct_answer": "determination"}, {"question": "\u2026\u2026\u2026. are stories that were made up by people who wanted to explain how our world works, such as how natural events occur.", "choices": ["Dreams", "Legends", "Lies", "Myths"], "correct_answer": "Myths"}, {"question": "With the help of the High Dam, the Nile no longer \u2026\u2026\u2026. as it used to.", "choices": ["irrigates", "moves", "floods", "rains"], "correct_answer": "floods"}, {"question": "The novel is greatly \u2026\u2026\u2026.; the author portrays the main character as more extreme or dramatic than he is.", "choices": ["exaggerated", "realistic", "authentic", "historic"], "correct_answer": "exaggerated"}, {"question": "Sorrowfully, the young man lost his mind and wounded his neighbour in a \u2026\u2026\u2026. of anger.", "choices": ["fat", "foot", "fit", "fete"], "correct_answer": "fit"}, {"question": "Stop being talkative; I\u201fm \u2026\u2026\u2026. up with your lies!", "choices": ["made", "fed", "given", "looked"], "correct_answer": "fed"}, {"question": "Our country will continue to make progress as long as sincere people \u2026\u2026\u2026.. .", "choices": ["disappear", "rest", "escape", "exist"], "correct_answer": "exist"}, {"question": "To\u2026\u2026\u2026. is to extend your arms and legs.", "choices": ["stretch out", "cheer up", "break down", "look back"], "correct_answer": "stretch out"}, {"question": "There should be a/an \u2026\u2026\u2026. decline in the national birth rate to achieve more development and raise standards of living.", "choices": ["instable", "fluctuating", "steady", "trifle"], "correct_answer": "steady"}, {"question": "Peter is an intelligent student, but he lacks\u2026\u2026\u2026. .", "choices": ["hesitation", "motivation", "retardation", "obstruction"], "correct_answer": "motivation"}, {"question": "Myths can be passed \u2026\u2026\u2026. from one generation to another.", "choices": ["in", "into", "on", "to"], "correct_answer": "on"}, {"question": "Peace is the backbone of stability and growth all across the world, so its spread is a matter of \u2026\u2026\u2026. concern.", "choices": ["minor", "local", "limited", "universal"], "correct_answer": "universal"}, {"question": "The police have strong\u2026\u2026\u2026. that the factory worker is the killer.", "choices": ["evidence", "cleverness", "eagerness", "dizziness"], "correct_answer": "evidence"}, {"question": "My friend is really\u2026\u2026\u2026.; he never brags about his achievements or possessions.", "choices": ["tolerate", "arrogant", "pompous", "humble"], "correct_answer": "humble"}, {"question": "The player behaved with great \u2026\u2026\u2026. towards his rival after he had won the game. He showed true nobility.",
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                      "choices": ["activity", "chivalry", "hatred", "envy"], "correct_answer": "chivalry"}, {"question": "Having healthy food and doing sports are the secrets of \u2026\u2026\u2026. youth.", "choices": ["external", "ordinary", "eternal", "limited"], "correct_answer": "eternal"}, {"question": "Myths and legends tell us about the \u2026\u2026\u2026. of people from the past.", "choices": ["perspectives", "failures", "humour", "laziness"], "correct_answer": "perspectives"}, {"question": "The purpose of \u2026\u2026\u2026. is to teach a lesson or moral. They are often about animals, plants or forces of nature.", "choices": ["myths", "fables", "superstitions", "lies"], "correct_answer": "fables"}, {"question": "My father was furious because I had lost my mobile. \u201cFurious\u201d here is similar in meaning to very \u201c\u2026\u2026\u2026. .\u201d", "choices": ["careful", "angry", "quiet", "astonished"], "correct_answer": "angry"}, {"question": "The thief was found \u2026\u2026\u2026. of stealing important objects from the museum, so he was sent to prison.", "choices": ["clear", "charged", "innocent", "guilty"], "correct_answer": "guilty"}, {"question": "My friend is always cautious; he doesn\u201ft want to \u2026\u2026\u2026. the risk.", "choices": ["appear", "do", "take", "leave"], "correct_answer": "take"}, {"question": "Although the young man was seriously wounded, he was \u2026\u2026\u2026. back to life.", "choices": ["given", "brought", "come", "appeared"], "correct_answer": "brought"}, {"question": "The manager gave us\u2026\u2026\u2026. instructions, which we received orally.", "choices": ["no", "written", "silent", "verbal"], "correct_answer": "verbal"}, {"question": "The earthquake has caused \u2026\u2026\u2026. results; it has destroyed a lot of houses.", "choices": ["tragic", "terrific", "relieving", "lies"], "correct_answer": "tragic"}, {"question": "Teens like playing video games because they offer a/an \u2026\u2026\u2026. to fantastic, unreal worlds with characters who have special powers.", "choices": ["rejection", "objection", "escape", "belief"], "correct_answer": "escape"}, {"question": "You must not \u2026\u2026\u2026. the law, or you will face consequences.", "choices": ["follow", "break", "obey", "make"], "correct_answer": "break"}, {"question": "Do you think your essay has any \u2026\u2026\u2026. to the topic we discussed? I don\u201ft think so.", "choices": ["consistence", "persistence", "insistence", "relevance"], "correct_answer": "relevance"}, {"question": "This young man has a place in my heart. This means:", "choices": ["I always remember his actions.", "He has a broken heart.", "I like him very much.", "I have a problem with him."], "correct_answer": "I like him very much."}, {"question": "Finally, the criminal paid with his life. This means:", "choices": ["He was sentenced to death as a result of his crimes.", "He had to pay a huge fine for his crime.", "He had to prove he was innocent.", "He was imprisoned for a short time."], "correct_answer": "He was sentenced to death as a result of his crimes."}]
